onetwotrade.com 2014-04-04

# Privacy Policy | OneTwoTrade

#### CLIENT AGREEMENT REGARDING USE OF ONETWOTRADE SERVICES

#### **Security and Privacy**

Your personal information and financial security is of utmost importance to us. We invest considerable resources to protect our customers’ privacy and use the most advanced, powerful security procedures and encryption systems available worldwide.

#### **What you can do**

**Identification**

Users access the system by entering a username and password. Your password is personal and must not be disclosed to others, not even to customer service personnel. Never save your username or password on or near a computer.

**Password**

Choose a password that cannot be easily deciphered, preferably consisting of random characters and digits. Change your password every three months. In the event that your password may have been revealed to others, please change it immediately.

**Logout**

At the end of any activity in the system, be sure to exit properly by clicking ‘Logout.’

**Encrypted Communications**

Either a closed lock or a complete key (depending upon which browser version is installed on your computer) should appear in your window when you execute transactions in your account. Double-clicking on this symbol will display the digital certificate issued to this site. Verify that the issuing organization is ‘Star Field Technology’ and that the certificate was issued to OneTwoTrade.

#### **Our promise to you**

We appreciate that you have provided us with your personal data. At OneTwoTrade, we strive to maintain the privacy of such information while helping you achieve your financial objectives. Access to the site system is secured and controlled by a Firewall that enables access only to those services that are required by the system. Information transmitted between the site and your personal computer is encrypted using a 256-bit SSL encryption certificate that has been provided for the site by ‘Star Field Technology.’ OneTwoTrade supervises and controls the systems' communications and records all activities taking place in the system. Routine information security checks are carried out by our information security experts.

Our Privacy Statement sets out the basis on which we process any personal data that we collect from you. If you have any questions, we are here to help 24/7.

#### **What Personal Information do we collect?**

We would typically collect the following information from you, whether you deal with OneTwoTrade as a private client, or otherwise in your individual capacity relating to a trust or investment vehicle established to invest on your behalf:

  1. Personal details such as name, age, occupation and marital status.
  2. Contact details such as address, telephone, email and in some cases, both private and work-related contact details.
  3. Identification documents such as your passport, copies which may generally include a head and shoulders photograph from, as applicable, your passport, national identity card or driver's license, as required by laws and regulations addressing due diligence and related matters.
  4. A personal identifier, depending on your country of residence.
  5. Extensive financial information, including source of wealth, investment experience and objectives, risk tolerance and, in certain jurisdictions, representations required under applicable law or regulation concerning your financial resources

If you deal withOneTwoTrade in the capacity of an officer, employee, director and/or principal of one of our corporate or institutional clients, the typical personal data we collect from you would include:

  1. Your name and contact details
  2. Your role/position/title and area of responsibility
  3. Certain identifying information (e.g. passport photo, etc.) as required by laws and regulations addressing money laundering and related matters.

You are not required to supply any of the personal data that we may request. However, failure to supply any of the personal data that we request may result in our being unable to open or maintain your account, or to provide services to you or your company. While we make every effort to ensure that all information we hold about you is accurate, complete and up to date, you can help us considerably in this regard by promptly notifying us if there are any changes to your personal information.

#### **How do we collect your personal information?**

We typically obtain personal data about you in the forms and documents used when you apply for an account with us, when you engage in transactions with us, when you access or use our products and services, or from third parties authorized to provide us with such information. We also collect personal data when we monitor or record our communications with you, or through use of certain technology as detailed further below.

#### **What are the purposes for which we use your Personal Data?**

We, our associated firms and/or other persons acting on our or their behalf may process and use your personal data to:

  * Administer and operate services in accordance with customer documents, including authorising or confirming transactions.
  * Carry out credit, money laundering and conflict checks with the purpose of fraud prevention purposes (and this may include consideration of information regarding political affiliations and criminal offences committed or alleged to have been committed) and to contact you about other services and products we offer.
  * Exercise and defend our legal rights.
  * Comply with legal and regulatory obligations and requests anywhere in the world (including reporting to and being audited by national and international regulatory, enforcement or exchange bodies and complying with court orders).
  * Record or monitor communications (including email, instant messaging, facsimile, telephone and other electronic communications) with you or your agent(s) for quality control and security purposes, as a record of your orders, instructions and related matters and in order to comply (and monitor compliance) with applicable laws and regulations, our agreements and any applicable policies and procedures; and as otherwise permitted under any applicable law or regulation.

#### **How do we use Cookies and similar technology?**

OneTwoTrade uses certain technology on its websites to collect information from visitors and compiles aggregate statistical information about how visitors use our websites, including information relating to the frequency of visits, IP addresses, the average length of visits, which pages are viewed during a visit and the effectiveness of advertising on our websites.

OneTwoTrade uses this information to improve the website content and performance. No individually identifiable information is collected for this purpose and OneTwoTrade does not monitor individual visitor behavior. Information held in cookies set by OneTwoTrade is kept to a minimum and can only be read by OneTwoTrade or by someone who has physical access to your personal computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer's hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalized service. They enable us to estimate our audience size and usage pattern, to store information about your preferences and to allow us to customize our site according to your individual interests in order to speed up your searches and to recognize you when you return to our site.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting, you may be unable to access certain parts of our site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log in to our site.

#### **How can you opt out of OneTwoTrade's mailing list?**

If you do not wish to receive any communications from OneTwoTrade, you may opt out of our mailing list by clicking the unsubscribe button at the end of our emails.

#### **When do we Disclose Personal Data we collect about you?**

Please be assured that OneTwoTrade does not sell, rent or trade your personal data. OneTwoTrade does not disclose your personal data, except as described in this Privacy Statement. Furthermore, third parties who process your personal data on our behalf are required to adhere to confidentiality standards with respect to such information. Our processing and use of your personal data, for the purposes specified in this Privacy Statement, may include disclosure of your personal data:

  * Between us and our associated firms, a list of which may be consulted in the corporate website of OneTwoTrade.
  * To other persons processing your personal data on our or their behalf or otherwise providing us or them with professional or other services.
  * To third parties such as settlement agents, overseas banks or exchange or clearing houses to whom we disclose in the course of providing products and services to you.
  * To credit reference, fraud prevention and other similar agencies and other financial institutions, with whose information to persons to whom we assign or novate our rights or obligations.
  * To prospective sellers or buyers in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, or if all or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  * To national and international regulatory, enforcement or exchange bodies or courts anywhere in the world as required by applicable law or regulations anywhere in the world or at their request.

#### **How do we protect the Security and Confidentiality of the personal data we collect about you?**

OneTwoTrade maintains appropriate physical, technical and procedural safeguards to protect any information that you provide to us from accidental or unauthorized loss, misuse, damage, modification, access or disclosure.

#### **OneTwoTrade has established an Information Security Team, which leads efforts to:**

  * Safeguard the confidentiality and privacy of information resources
  * Properly classify information resources.
  * Meet legal and regulatory obligations concerning the protection of information resources.
  * Implement and maintain information security policies and procedures. 
  * Integrate protection of information resources into the process life cycles of the business.
  * Educate those working for or on behalf of Banc De Binary on information security policies and responsibilities.
  * Authenticate users and limit access to information resources based on authorization that has been granted.

#### **What rights do you have under European Data Protection Laws?**

If you wish to access a copy of your personal data, or you wish to modify any personal data we hold about you, or you want us to cease processing any of your personal data held by us and/or our associated firms, you can do so by written request to our Data Protection Counsel at the address listed below. In the case of a request to access personal data, we and our associated firms reserve the right to charge an appropriate fee, if applicable. You may be required to supply a valid means of identification as a security precaution in order to assist us in preventing the unauthorized disclosure of your personal data. We will process your request within the time provided by applicable law.

#### **How do we update this Privacy Statement?**

We may change or update portions of this Privacy Statement to reflect changes in our practices and/or applicable law and regulation. Please check this Privacy Statement from time to time so you are aware of any changes or updates to the Privacy Statement, which may be indicated by a change in the effective date noted at the beginning of the Privacy Statement.
